Guide to the David Benjamin Mixner Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audiovisual, 1924, 1964-2004; Series VI
  - Videotapes
    - Personal
      - Baby Monk Seal, Kauai, Hawaii, 1991 July; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
      - Baldwin, Tammy, "Happy Birthday David", 2000 August 10; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
      - Bradley/David tape, 1990; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
      - Easter and Hawaii, 1988; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
      - Family vacation, Hawaii, 1991 July; videotape (VHS) (Box 70)
      - Lake Arrowhead, 1989 August; 1 (Box 70)
      - Mixner, David
        - Farewell, 1989; 1 (Box 70)
        - Tribute testimonials [by Patsy Annison, Rob Eichberg, Judge Steve Lachs, Alex Koleszar, Bill Press, Roberta Bennett, Diane Abbitt, Scott Hitt, Mary Louise Oates, Tanya Domi, Jeremy Bernard, Bob Hattoy; 11 videotapes (includes VHS, Betacam, Betacam-SP, and U-matic), 1993 January 11; 11 (Box 70–72)
      - President Clinton Remarks for the David Mixner Birthday Celebration, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 2000 August 11 (Box 72)
      - Stranger Among Friends, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 (Box 72)
        - Use copies (duplicate copies), 2 commercially produced videotapes (VHS) (Box 72)
      - Summer Sunday USA (Show #7), 1984 August 17; 1 (Box 72)
      - Thanksgiving reunion in Denver (duplicate copies), 1989; 2 (Box 72)
      - Xmas, 1987; 1 (Box 72)
    - Appearances and interviews
      - Against All Odds, commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 73)
      - Bantam Books [interview with I. Applebaum, Bob Weisbach, and Mixner; ], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 January 5 (Box 73)
      - Charlie Rose, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 July 23 (Box 73)
      - CNBC [Charles Grodin interview], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 July 23 (Box 73)
      - "A Conversation with DBM" ["A Salute to David Mixner"; includes testimonials from 1960s-1990s] (duplicate copies), 3 commercially produced videotapes (VHS and U-matic), 1993 January 15 (Box 73)
      - Dateline, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 July 10 (Box 73)
      - Face the Nation [discussion of same-sex marriages] (duplicate copies), 2 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1996 May 26 (Box 73)
      - Get Used to It
        - "Homosexual Victims of the Holocaust" [with Ted Phillips, Roberta Bennett, and Mixner], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1999 November (Box 73)
        - "Sex and Morality" [with Sue Burnside, Sky Johnson, and Mixner], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1998 October (Box 73)
        - "State of the Community" [with Torie Osborn, Roland Palencia, and Mixner], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 2001 November (Box 74)
        - "Voices of Our Lives: David Mixner," commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 August (Box 74)
      - Good Morning America, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 July 15 (Box 74)
      - Inside Politics [2 versions; one includes interview on gays in the military, undated], 2 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1995 June 12 (Box 74)
      - "An Important Message from Gov. Ann Richards and David Mixner" [Garry Mauro Campaign], commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 74)
      - Nightline, "Trial Balloon on Gays on [sic] Military?", commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 74)
      - Sunday Morning, "Back to Chicago", commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1996 August 25 (Box 74)
      - Wake Up with Writers (duplicate copies), 3 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1996 June 17 (Box 74)
      - Washington interview [associated with Mixner tribute dinner], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1993 January (Box 75)
      - Week in Review [2 shows], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1993 September 19, 1996 July 12 (Box 75)
      - "The Whole World Was Watching" [a production of ABC News] (duplicate copies), 2 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1998 December 10 (Box 75)
    - Events
      - Access Now for Gay and Lesbian Equality (ANGLE) dinner [3 digital Betacam, 2 VHS], 1999 October 2, 18; 5 (Box 76)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AmFAR) (duplicate copies), 5 videotapes (VHS), 1994 March 3 (Box 77)
      - Asian/Pacific Gays and Friends (APGF) installation dinner, 1998; videotape (VHS) (Box 77)
      - California AIDS Ride [New Line Cinema], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1994 August 30 (Box 77)
      - Clinton, William Jefferson, rally at the Palace, Hollywood (duplicate copies), 1992 May 18
        - 3 videotapes (VHS) (Box 77)
        - 2 videotapes (VHS) (Box 78)
      - General Conference XVI, Phoenix, Arizona [Metropolitan Community Church; Mixner speaking], 3 videotapes (VHS), 1993 (Box 78)
      - The Great Peace March [ CBS Morning News, Today Show, PSA ], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1985 October-November (Box 78)
      - Hart, Lucille, dinner, 1993; videotape (VHS) (Box 78)
      - Human Rights Campaign, undated; 2 (Box 78)
      - March on Washington [Mixner speaking], 1993 (Box 78)
        - ABC, commercially produced videotape (VHS) (Box 78)
        - C-SPAN, commercially produced videotape (VHS) (Box 79)
      - National Press Club (NPC) luncheon, 6 videotapes (VHS), 1993 April 23 (Box 79)
      - One Year After the Historic March on Washington, D.C., commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1988 (Box 79)
      - Victory Fund
        - Mixner tribute event, 1993 January 11
          - Achtenberg, Roberta, interview, videotape (VHS) (Box 79)
          - Brown, Art, interview, videotape (VHS) (Box 80)
        - Feinstein, Dianne, studio shoot, 1993 January 12; 2 (Box 80)
        - "Recognizing Our Own'" videotape (VHS), undated; 1 (Box 80)
        - A Salute to David Mixner [3 Betacam-SP and 4 VHS], 1993 January 19; 7 (Box 80)
        - Untitled event, 1994; 1 (Box 80)
    - Other
      - Cable Positive, 1999 April 21; 1 (Box 81)
      - Change in the Air: Is the Military Ban Going Away? (Network Q), commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1993 January (Box 81)
      - Clinton, William Jefferson
        - "The Man from Hope", commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1992 July 21 (Box 81)
        - "Two-Steppin' for the Cure," 3 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1994 February 26 (Box 81)
        - Weekend Today: "Gays & Clinton," commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1992 December 9 (Box 81)
        - Untitled, 1992 May 20; 1 (Box 81)
      - "Conduct Unbecoming: Gays & Lesbians in the U.S. Military," commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1994 (Box 81)
      - Dish [with Mixner], 1994; videotape (VHS) (Box 81)
      - "The Erotic Impressions of Philip Hitchcock" (Playboy Television's Sexcetera ), commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 82)
      - Estes Park, 2 videotapes (VHS), 1989 February (Box 82)
      - "Gay Rights" (Warren Olney, News 13), commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 82)
      - "Get Used to It 'Year of the Queer?'" (Citychannel 10), commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1994 January 1 (Box 82)
      - Hale House Dinner Documentary: "Celebrating 30 Years," commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 82)
      - Horizons Community Services, 1996 March 14; videotape (VHS) (Box 82)
      - In the Life
        - Fall series premiere, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1992 November (Box 82)
        - "June Pride Episode," commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1999 Jun/July (Box 82)
        - Untitled, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1994 March 29 (Box 82)
      - Interviews
        - Koleszar, Alex, with Bill Press, Patsy Annison, Rob Eichberg, and Steve Lachs, undated; 1 (Box 83)
        - Lachs, Steve, with Roberta Bennett, Diane Abbitt, Scott Hitt, undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 83)
      - "Kennedy Speech," commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1993 March 30; 1 (Box 83)
      - Los Angeles Olympics, 1984; videotape (VHS) (Box 83)
      - Lowe, Rob, tape, undated; 1 (Box 83)
      - March in April [Pride film], commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated; 1 (Box 83)
      - Mauro for Governor Gay Tape, commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated; 1 (Box 83)
      - Mixner, David B., "Demo Reel," [VHS and Betacam-SP], 1997 April 25; 2 (Box 83)
      - Mixner et al., undated; 1 (Box 83)
      - Mixner, undated; 1 (Box 83)
      - National Association for the Advancement of Colored Persons (NAACP): Dewey Obenchain Films
        - Coming to Life, 3 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1999 October 25 (Box 84)
        - House on Fire, 3 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1999 October 25, November 8 (Box 84)
        - Sister's Keeper, 3 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1999 October 25, November 5 (Box 84)
      - 1988-A Gay Review [Lifestyle Update Productions], commercially produced videotape (VHS) (Box 84)
      - 1987-A Gay Review [Lifestyle Update Productions], commercially produced videotape (VHS) (Box 85)
      - "Out Loud" [Miriam Bjerre], commercially produced videotape (VHS), undated (Box 85)
      - Out Across America [Network Q], commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1993 March (Box 85)
      - "A Step Toward Tomorrow", undated; videotape (VHS) (Box 85)
      - To Support & Defend: The Role of Homosexuals in the Military, commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1993 (Box 85)
      - Vic Ferrer Productions
        - "Because the Night," "Friends in Love," "Stonewall Legacy," commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1994 June 13 (Box 85)
        - "Our Time Has Come," commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1994 June 13 (Box 85)
      - Voices of Our Lives: Paul Monette (Citychannel 10), commercially produced videotape (VHS), 1993 September (Box 85)
      - "We Were Marked with a Big A": Persecution of Homosexuals in the Third Reich (United States Holocaust Memorial Council), 2 commercially produced videotapes (VHS), 1994 February 28 (Box 85)
- Additional Material, 1998-2006; Accession 2007-M-002
  This accession comprises subject files and correspondence, including email printouts.
  - Subject files
    - Annison book, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - China August trip, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Fortune Society, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Gay
      - International, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Marriage, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Vote, 1998-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Hacket, Paul, for Senate, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Hindery [Leo]--Ferrer [Fernando] for Mayor, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Houghton Group, 1999, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Human Rights Campaign, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - ITAC [International Treatment Access Coalition], 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Maloney [Sean] for Attorney General, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 12 - 13)
    - Newsom [Gavin] for Mayor, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Poverty Project
      - 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - East Carroll, LA, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Expenses, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Foundations, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - McDowell County, WV, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Published, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Starr County, TX, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Ziebach County, SD, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Robinson [Ken]/Koemer [Sonny]
      - Memoranda, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Reports, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Showtime Gay TV, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Transatlantic Partnership Against AIDS, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 26 - 27)
    - Ukraine, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Victory Fund 2005 Event (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - West Virginia
      - Articles/background, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Community organization, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Contacts, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Danielson, Michael, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Memoranda, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Statistics, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence
    - Cards and letters, 2005-2006, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Email
      - 2005 Oct-2006 Apr (Box 2, Folder 37 - 79)
      - 2006 Apr-Aug (Box 3, Folder 80 - 116)
- Additional Material, 2006; Accession 2007-M-041
  This accession comprises correspondence in the form of email printouts.
  - Correspondence, 2006 September-December (Box 1, Folder 1-37)
- Additional Material, 2001-2009; Accession 2007-M-097
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Includes accessions 2007-M-097, 2008-M-019, 2008-M-061, 2009-M-012, 2009-M-032, 2009-M-049, 2009-M-077, 2009-M-096, 2010-M-028, 2010-M-032, 2010-M-042, 2010-M-044, 2010-M-056, 2010-M-071, and 2010-M-086.
  These accessions comprise correspondence in the form of email printouts and subject files.
  Arrangement
  Correspondence is arranged chronologically; subject files are arranged by accession.
  - Correspondence
    - 2007 Jan-May (Box 1, Folder 1-36)
    - 2007 Jun-Sep (Box 2, Folder 37-69)
    - 2007 Oct-2008 Feb (Box 3, Folder 1-31)
    - 2008 Mar-May (Box 5, Folder 1-13)
    - 2008 May 13-Jul, 2008 May 13-July (Box 6, Folder 1-13)
    - 2008 Jul (Box 7, Folder 1-5)
    - 2008 Aug-Sep (Box 8, Folder 1-11)
    - 2008 Sep-Oct (Box 9, Folder 1-13)
    - 2008 Oct 21-Nov (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
    - 2008 Nov-Dec (Box 11, Folder 1-20)
    - 2009 Jan-Mar (Box 13, Folder 1-12)
    - 2009 Apr-Jun (Box 14, Folder 1-34)
    - 2009 Jun-Aug (Box 15, Folder 1-31)
    - 2009 Sep (Box 16, Folder 1-27)
    - 2009 Oct (Box 18, Folder 1-31)
    - 2009 Nov-Dec (Box 19, Folder 1-27)
    - 2010 Jan (Box 20, Folder 1-15)
    - 2010 Feb 28-May 19 (Box 20, Folder 16-26)
      Some of the email messages overlap with previously accessioned email messages.
    - 2010 Mar (Box 21, Folder 1-21)
    - 2010 Apr (Box 22, Folder 1-15)
    - 2010 May (Box 22, Folder 16-27)
  - Subject files
    - Additional Material, Accession 2008-M-061
      - Amsterdam, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Articles and clippings, 2005-2007 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
      - Big Sky Project, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
      - Calendar, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Cards and notes, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Edwards for President, 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 8-10)
      - Elected officials, Circa 2007-2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Equality Rides, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Feingold for President, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 13-17)
      - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Shuster Projects, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Victory Fund event, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - World AIDS Campaign, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Writers Union, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Additional Material, Accession 2009-M-049
      - American Academy of HIV Medicine (AAHIVM), 2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Articles and letters, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - DavidMixner.com, 2006-2008 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
      - Hindery, Leo/Intermedia, 2006-2008 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Hindery, Leo/Political, 2006-2008 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Jacob's Ladder, 2005-2008 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
      - Maloney for Attorney General, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Mothers2Mothers (m2m), 2008 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Obama for President, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 11-13)
      - Suddenly A Soldier, 2001-2007 (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
    - Additional Material, Accession 2010-M-032
      - Annison, draft changes, Circa 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - Articles, cards, and notes, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - The Dunes of Overeen, legal, 2000-2005 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Hindery political, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Mixner, David Benjamin, biographical material and writings, 1993-2002 (Box 16, Folder 32-33)
      - Newsom for Mayor, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - On the Edge, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Point Foundation leadership conference, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Presidential appointments, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Additional Material, Accession 2010-M-056
      - Photographs of Gay Vets Memorial Service and holiday card, 2009, undated (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Additional Material, Accession 2010-M-071
      - Photographs of David Mixner and others, 2003-2007 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Additional Material, Accession 2010-M-086
      - Notecards, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Photographs of Mixner and others, 1999-2007, undated (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Printed material
        - Point Foundation reception program, Point Honors, New York, 2010 April (Box 22, Folder 30)
          Point Foundation is the nation's largest scholar-granting organization for LGBT students of merit.
        - Becoming Visible: Portraits of homeless transgendered teenagers, promotional flyer for the exhibit, 2010 April (Box 22, Folder 30)
        - dcagenda: the lgbtq community's new source, vol. 2, issue 14, 2010 April 2 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Additional Material, 1969-2010; Accession 2011-M-010
  - Correspondence
    - 2010 May-July (Box 1, Folder 1-31)
    - 2010 July-August (Box 2, Folder 1-8)
  - Audiovisual
    Material is listed aplphabetically.
    - ABC News [commercially produced], 1969 October 1; 1 (Box 3)
    - ABC News, "The Whole World Was Watching" [commercially produced], 1998; 1 (Box 4)
      A report by Diane Sawyer and Connie Chung includes an interview with David Mixner discussing the Chicago Democratic Convention of 1968.
    - Ask Not, directed by Johnny Symons [commercially produced], 2008; 1 (Box 5)
      - Use copy (Box 5U)
    - Characters Unite National Town Hall [commercially produced], 2009 December 2 (Box 6)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 6U)
    - Charlie Rose [commercially produced], 1996 July 23; 1 (Box 7)
      Show includes an interview with David Mixner, discussing his memoir, Stranger Among Friends.
    - Chicago Children's Choir: Songs on the Road to Freedom [commercially produced], 2008; 1 (Box 8)
    - City of West Hollywood, Citychannel 10, Get Used To It, show #100 [commercially produced], 2003 June; 1 (Box 9)
    - CNN [commercially produced], 2003 November; 1 (Box 10)
    - Dateline: Tom Brokaw, "Eyewitness to History" [commercially produced], 2005 January 22; 1 (Box 11)
    - Empire State Pride Agenda fall dinner: David Mixner speech [commercially produced], 2007 (Box 12)
      - Use copy (Box 12U)
    - For the Bible Tells Me So [commercially produced], 2007; 1 (Box 13)
    - Fox News [commercially produced], 2003 December 1; 1 (Box 14)
    - The Gay and Lesbian Community Welcomes You to a Special Evening with President William Jefferson Clinton, Beverly Hilton Hotel, Los Angeles [commercially produced], 1999 October 2; 1 (Box 15)
    - Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund Salute to David Mixner [commercially produced], 1993 January 19 (Box 16)
    - Metropolitan Community Church General Conference XVI, Phoenix, Arizona [commercially produced], 1993; 1 (Box 17)
    - National Press Club speech by David Mixner [commercially produced], 1993 April 23; 1 (Box 18)
    - Nineteenth Annual GLAAD Media Awards, San Francisco [commercially produced], 2008 May 10; 1 (Box 19)
      - Pioneer Award: David Mixner [commercially produced], 2008; 1 (Box 20)
        Tribute video clip shown during awards ceremony.
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 20U)
    - Photographs from debate at Oxford, 2008 October 23-24; 1 (Box 21)
    - Point Foundation, "2010 Point Honors New York" [commercially produced], 2010 April 19
      - Tape #1, 1 (Box 22)
      - Tape #2, 1 (Box 23)
      - Tape #3, 1 (Box 24)
      - Message to David Mixner from Prime Minister and Mrs. Brown, 1 (Box 25)
        Recorded tribute aired during presentation of award to David Mixner.
    - PRO-Peace
      - Documentary [commercially produced], 1985; 1 (Box 26)
        Video runs for 9 minutes.
      - CBS Morning News, Maria Shriver [commercially produced], 1985 October 14; 1 (Box 27)
      - Today Show, Jane Pauley [commercially produced], 1985 November 22; 1 (Box 27)
      - Public Service Announcement [commercially produced], 1985; 1 (Box 27)
    - Proposition Apartheid promotion [commercially produced], 2010; 1 (Box 28)
    - Read Street Festival and Second District New Democratic Club highlights, Baltimore, Maryland, Circa 1970; 1 (Box 29)
      There is no audio on this recording.
    - Tomb of the Unknown Soldier: Leonard Matlovich Memorial and DADT (Don't Ask, Don't Tell) Protest [commercially produced], 2009 October 10; 1 (Box 30)
    - "Unlikely Allies", New York Times Company LGBT and Allies event [commercially produced], 2010 March 10; 1 (Box 31)
- Additional Material, 2010; Accession 2011-M-027
  This accession comprises correspondence in the form of email printouts, and a small number of subject files.
  - Correspondence, 2010 August-September (Box 1, Folder 1-29)
  - Subject files
    - Cards and invitations, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - "I Do: The History of Marriage in America" brochure, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Additional Material, 2010; Accession 2011-M-038
  - Correspondence, 2010 September-November (Box 1, Folder 1-26)
  - Subject files
    - Krueger, Jordan P., "American Equality Campaign: A New Direction for the LGBT Community", 2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Out Magazine invitation to "Out100", November 18, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Additional Material, 2010; Accession 2011-M-045
  - Correspondence, 2010 November-December (Box 1, Folder 1-29)
  - Subject files
    - Cards and invitations, Circa 2010 November-December (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Interview, 2010 November (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Additional Material, 2011; Accession 2011-M-054
  This accession comprises correspondence in the form of email printouts
  - Correspondence, 2011 January-February (Box 1, Folder 1-29)
- Additional Material, Accession 2011-M-078
  This accession comprises correspondence in the form of email printouts and a small number of cards and notes.
  - Correspondence, 2011 February-April (Box 1, Folder 1-28)
  - Computer files (Box 2–3)
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
- Additional Material, 2011; Accession 2011-M-090
  - Correspondence, 2011 April-May (Box 1, Folder 1-27)
- Additional Material, 2011 June; Accession 2012-M-001
  - Correspondence, 2011 June (Box 1, Folder 1-15)
  - Correspondence, 2011 June (Box 2, Folder 1-11)
- Additional Material, Circa 1950-2011; Accession 2012-M-005
  - Correspondence, 2011 July (Box 1, Folder 1-11)
  - Correspondence, 2011 July (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Photographs, Circa 1950-1964, undated
    - Circa 1950-1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Photographs of David with family, classmates and Boy Scout troop, circa 1950-1960.
    - 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Separated Materials
      Photographs of David, classmates, and friends taken at the New York World's Fair, the youth parade, the prom, after prom and the boardwalk at Ocean City, New Jersey.
- Additional Material, 2011; Accession 2012-M-021
  This accession comprises correspondence in the form of email printouts and a small number of birthday cards.
  - Correspondence, 2011 August-September (Box 1, Folder 1-25)
  - Birthday greetings for Mixner's sixty-fifth birthday, 2011 August (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Includes a greeting from Mayor Michael R. Bloomberg thanking Mixner for his work on New York's Marriage Equality Act.
- Additional Material, 1990-2011; Accession 2012-M-028
  - Correspondence, 2011 October (Box 1, Folder 1-14)
  - Correspondence, 2011 November (Box 2, Folder 1-10)
  - Manuscript of the Mixner family genealogy by Patricia Mixner Annison, David's sister., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Additional Material, 1930-2011; Accession 2012-M-039
  - Correspondence, 2011 November-2011 December (Box 1, Folder 1-11)
  - Correspondence, 2011 December (Box 2, Folder 1-7)
  - Manuscript of the the Mixner family genealogy, part II, 1930-1945 (Box 2, Folder 8-10)